<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ruoyu Deng</title>
    <link>https://dengruoyu.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ruoyu Deng</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://dengruoyu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy in Data Sharing (cooperate with 360 company)</title>
      <link>https://dengruoyu.github.io/project/360/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dengruoyu.github.io/project/360/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Deep learning requires a large amount of data in training. In many cases, we cannot get enough data we needed to train a deep learning model. Data are distributed in many owners. Due to privacy considerations, we cannot gather these data directly. A proper method for data sharing without privacy leakage is needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a project cooperating with 360.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FraudJudger: Real-World Data Oriented Fraud Detection on Digital Payment Platforms</title>
      <link>https://dengruoyu.github.io/publication/conference-paper/fraudjudger-real-world-data-oriented-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dengruoyu.github.io/publication/conference-paper/fraudjudger-real-world-data-oriented-fraud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Abstract:&lt;/em&gt; Automated fraud behaviors detection on electronic payment
platforms is a tough problem. Fraud users often exploit the
vulnerability of payment platforms and the carelessness of
users to defraud money, steal passwords, do money laundering, etc, which causes enormous losses to digital payment
platforms and users. There are many challenges for fraud
detection in practice. Traditional fraud detection methods
require a large-scale manually labeled dataset, which is hard
to obtain in reality. Manually labeled data cost tremendous
human efforts. Besides, the continuous and rapid evolution
of fraud users makes it hard to find new fraud patterns based
on existing detection rules. In our work, we propose a realworld data oriented detection paradigm which can detect
fraud users and upgrade its detection ability automatically.
Based on the new paradigm, we design a novel fraud detection model, FraudJudger, to analyze users behaviors on
digital payment platforms and detect fraud users with fewer
labeled data in training. FraudJudger can learn the latent
representations of users from unlabeled data with the help of
Adversarial Autoencoder (AAE). Furthermore, FraudJudger
can find new fraud patterns from unknown users by cluster
analysis. Our experiment is based on a real-world electronic
payment dataset. Comparing with other well-known fraud
detection methods, FraudJudger can achieve better detection
performance with only 10% labeled data.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fraud Detection on tiancheng (cooperate with tiancheng company)</title>
      <link>https://dengruoyu.github.io/project/tiancheng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dengruoyu.github.io/project/tiancheng/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-description&#34;&gt;Project Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Automated fraud behaviors detection on electronic payment
platforms is a tough problem. Fraud users often exploit the
vulnerability of payment platforms and the carelessness of
users to defraud money, steal passwords, do money laundering, etc, which causes enormous losses to digital payment
platforms and users. There are many challenges for fraud
detection in practice. Traditional fraud detection methods
require a large-scale manually labeled dataset, which is hard
to obtain in reality. Manually labeled data cost tremendous
human efforts. Besides, the continuous and rapid evolution
of fraud users makes it hard to find new fraud patterns based
on existing detection rules. In our work, we propose a real-world data oriented detection paradigm which can detect
fraud users and upgrade its detection ability automatically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;model-overview&#34;&gt;Model Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Model overview&#34; src=&#34;paper.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the overview of our detection model.
Our
model should contain two main functions: building fraud
users blacklist and automatically updating the blacklist. The whole
detection model contains three phases:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phase I:&lt;/strong&gt; Merging features from raw data. Platforms collect two main classes of information: operation data and
transaction data. We first merge the two classes data, and
the merged features are passed to our fraud detection part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phase II:&lt;/strong&gt; Building fraud users blacklist. Merged features
in Phase I are of high dimensions, which can not be used
directly. We can omit ineffective and noisy features and get
efficient low dimension features with the help of adversarial
autoencoder. In the meantime, we can detect fraud users by
a few labeled data. It is a semi-supervised learning process.
Detected fraud users will be added in the blacklist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phase III:&lt;/strong&gt; Updating fraud users blacklist by cluster analysis. The key idea is to find new fraud users beyond existing
detection rules. In this phase, we train a new AAE network
without labels to learn the latent representations of users.
Then we cluster these latent variables from the network.
After clustering latent variables, different users groups are
formed. We detect fraud users with new patterns from these
fraud groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The details of our research is shown in our paper &lt;a href=&#34;https://dry999.github.io/publication/conference-paper/fraudjudger-real-world-data-oriented-fraud/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;FraudJudger: Real-World Data Oriented Fraud Detection on Digital Payment Platforms&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a project cooperating with tiancheng.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpamTracer: Manual Fake Review Detection for O2O Commercial Platforms by Using Geolocation Features</title>
      <link>https://dengruoyu.github.io/publication/conference-paper/spamtracer-manual-fake-review-detection-for-o2o-commercial-platforms-by-using-geolocation-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dengruoyu.github.io/publication/conference-paper/spamtracer-manual-fake-review-detection-for-o2o-commercial-platforms-by-using-geolocation-features/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Abstract：&lt;/em&gt; Nowadays, O2O commercial platforms are playing a crucial
role in our daily purchases. However, some people are trying to manipulate the online market maliciously by opinion spamming, a kind of web
fraud behavior like writing fake reviews, due to fame and profits, which
will harm online purchasing environment and should be detected and
eliminated. Moreover, manual fake reviewers are more deceptive compared with old web spambots. Although several efficient methods were
proposed in the fake review detection field, the manual fake reviewers
are also evolving rapidly. They imitate to be benign users to control
the velocity of review fraud actions, and deceive the detection system.
Our investigation presented that geolocation factor is potential and can
well reflect the distinctions between fake reviewers and benign users. In
this research, we analyzed the geolocations of shops in reviews, found
the distinct distribution features of those in fake reviewers and benign
users, and proposed a SpamTracer model that can identify fake reviewers and benign users by exploiting an improved HMM(Hidden Markov
Model). Our experiment demonstrated that SpamTracer could achieve
71% accuracy and 76% recall in the unbalanced dataset, outperforming
some excellent classical approaches in the aspect of stability. Furthermore, SpamTracer can help to analyze the regularities of review fraud
actions. Those regularities reflect the time and location in which online
shops are likely to hire fake reviewers to increase their turnover. We also
found that a small group of fake reviewers tend to work with plural shops
located in a small business zone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
