<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3 on Ruoyu Deng</title>
    <link>https://dengruoyu.github.io/publication_types/3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3 on Ruoyu Deng</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://dengruoyu.github.io/publication_types/3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FraudJudger: Real-World Data Oriented Fraud Detection on Digital Payment Platforms</title>
      <link>https://dengruoyu.github.io/publication/conference-paper/fraudjudger-real-world-data-oriented-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dengruoyu.github.io/publication/conference-paper/fraudjudger-real-world-data-oriented-fraud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Abstract:&lt;/em&gt; Automated fraud behaviors detection on electronic payment
platforms is a tough problem. Fraud users often exploit the
vulnerability of payment platforms and the carelessness of
users to defraud money, steal passwords, do money laundering, etc, which causes enormous losses to digital payment
platforms and users. There are many challenges for fraud
detection in practice. Traditional fraud detection methods
require a large-scale manually labeled dataset, which is hard
to obtain in reality. Manually labeled data cost tremendous
human efforts. Besides, the continuous and rapid evolution
of fraud users makes it hard to find new fraud patterns based
on existing detection rules. In our work, we propose a realworld data oriented detection paradigm which can detect
fraud users and upgrade its detection ability automatically.
Based on the new paradigm, we design a novel fraud detection model, FraudJudger, to analyze users behaviors on
digital payment platforms and detect fraud users with fewer
labeled data in training. FraudJudger can learn the latent
representations of users from unlabeled data with the help of
Adversarial Autoencoder (AAE). Furthermore, FraudJudger
can find new fraud patterns from unknown users by cluster
analysis. Our experiment is based on a real-world electronic
payment dataset. Comparing with other well-known fraud
detection methods, FraudJudger can achieve better detection
performance with only 10% labeled data.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
